<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoGoSushi</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="descriptions">Brand owner: Pernod Ricard Winemakers Head office: Level 3, 16 Byfield Street, North Ryde, NSW 2113 Australia Tel: +61 2 8874 8222 Website: jacobscreek.com Marketing director: Derek Oliver Product range: Reserve, Classic, Sparkling, Cool Harvest, Twin Pickings, Moscato, Heritage, Winemakers Selection (China only), 1837 The Solway (China only), WAH, Lamoon, Double Barrel, Earth Vine Grape, Two Lands (US only) Volume 2013: 6.6m 9l cases Volume 2014: 6m 9l cases Change: -9% Holding onto its place in this year’s rankings despite a small slide is Pernod Ricard’s biggest selling wine brand, whose global ambitions appear to be firmly on the rise following the 2014 unveiling of its new logo. On the product front, 2014 saw Jacob’s Creek embrace Italian varieties before further flexing its innovative muscles to draw on the spirits expertise of its parent company with the launch of Double Barrel, a Barossa Shiraz and Coonawarra Cabernet Sauvignon finished in whisky casks. In the wake of Pernod Ricard’s high profile acquisition of Kenwood Vineyards in Sonoma, the group took a further step to strengthen its US presence by bringing Napa winemaker Ehren Jordan over the Australia in order to create a Jacob’s Creek expression specially designed for the US market. The resulting “Two Lands” range hit US shelves in March 2015. It’s not just new product development keeping the brand busy: Jacob’s Creek signed none other than international tennis star Novak Djokovic to front the latest instalment of its “Made By” film series. This is being backed up by a multi-million pound UK marketing campaign for 2015, also being rolled out across Canada, China and Australia, which features the people and places behind the Jacob’s Creek brand in a big to highlight its Australian heritage and provenance. </string>
</resources>
